Finding Aid for the Kelly Miller Smith Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- SUBJECT FILES
  - Fund of Renewal — American Baptist Churches, USA, 1975 - 1976 (Box 60, Folder 19)
  - Fund of Renewal — Newsletters (Box 60, Folder 20)
  - Fund of Renewal — Publication (Box 60, Folder 21)
  - Girl Scout Meeting, 1981 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Girl Scouts, 1979 (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Girl Scouts, 1980 (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Girl Scouts, 1981 (Box 61, Folder 4 - 5)
  - Girl Scouts, 1982 (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - Goodwill Industries of Middle Tennessee, Inc. (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - "The Gospel and Power" (essay, unidentified) (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - Governmental and Legislative Matters (Box 61, Folder 9)
  - Greater Cleveland Growth Corp. — Executive Committee (Box 61, Folder 10)
  - Greater Cleveland Growth Corp. — Revenue and Application (Box 61, Folder 11)
  - Hand Gun Control (Box 61, Folder 12)
  - Handicapped (Box 61, Folder 13)
  - Harvard Divinity School (Box 61, Folder 14)
  - Harvard University Club (Box 61, Folder 15)
  - Henri O'Bryant Choir Robes (Box 61, Folder 16)
  - Highlander Folk School (Box 61, Folder 17)
  - Historic Articles (Box 61, Folder 18)
  - Holland, Germany and Africa Trip, 1972 (Box 61, Folder 19)
  - Housing Affairs (Box 61, Folder 20)
  - Howard Thurman Educational Trust (Box 61, Folder 21)
  - Howard University (Box 62, Folder 1 - 2)
  - Howard University — Clippings (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Howard University School of Religion — Annual Report, 1969 - 1970 (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Howard University School of Religion, 1970 - 1971 (Box 62, Folder 5 - 6)
  - Howard University School of Religion — Conference on the Black Religious Experience and Theological Education (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Howard University School of Religion - - Clippings (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Hubbard Hospital (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - In Roads (Box 62, Folder 10)
  - Institute of Services to Education (Carl H. Marbury) (Box 62, Folder 11)
  - Institute of the Black World, 1970 - 1973 (Box 62, Folder 12)
  - Institute of the Black World, 1974 - 1976 (Box 62, Folder 13)
  - Interchurch Committee on Housing (Box 62, Folder 14)
  - Interdenominational Conference of Furlough Missionaries (Box 62, Folder 15)
  - Interdenominational Ministers Fellowship (IMF), 1971 - 1976 (Box 62, Folder 16)
  - Interdenominational Ministers Fellowship (IMF), 1977 - 1978 (Box 62, Folder 17)
  - Interdenominational Ministers Fellowship (IMF), 1979 - 1983 (Box 62, Folder 18)
  - Interdenominational Ministers Fellowship (IMF) - - Bills Paid (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Interdenominational Ministers Fellowship (IMF) - - Financial Reports (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Interdenominational Ministers Fellowship (IMF) - - Invoices (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Interdenominational Ministers Fellowship (IMF) - - Miscellaneous (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Interdenominational Ministers Fellowship (IMF) Emergency Fund (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Interdenominational Theological Center (ITC), 1970 - 1974 (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - Interdenominational Theological Center (ITC), 1975 - 1977 (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - Interdenominational Theological Center (ITC), 1978 - 1981 (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Interfaith Association (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - Inter-Group Coordinating Committee (Box 63, Folder 10)
  - International Christian Youth Exchange (ICYE) (Box 63, Folder 11)
  - International Freedom Mobilization (IFM); South Africa Freedom Committee (Box 63, Folder 12)
  - International Preview Society (Box 63, Folder 13)
  - International Student Conference — Williamsburg, VA, 1971 (Box 63, Folder 14)
  - Interreligious Foundation for Community Organization, Inc. (IFCO) (Box 63, Folder 15 - 17)
  - J.A. Middleton and Association (Box 63, Folder 18)
  - James Hendrix Banquet (Box 63, Folder 19)
  - Jesse W. Jackson's Dissertation Committee — Sociology (Box 63, Folder 20)
  - Jewish Federation of Nashville (Box 63, Folder 21)
  - Jimmy Sensing — Medical Home Care (Box 63, Folder 22)
  - John Milton Society for the Blind (Box 63, Folder 23)
  - Joint Evangelistic Conference (Box 63, Folder 24)
  - Journal for Ecumenical Studies (Box 63, Folder 25)
  - Journal of Religious Education (A.M.E. Church) (Box 63, Folder 26)
  - Katallagete (Box 64, Folder 1 - 2)
  - KMS Story - - Jean Morton (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - King, Barbara (Atlanta) (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - King, Martin Luther, Jr. (Box 64, Folder 5 - 12)
  - King, Martin Luther, Jr. — Clippings (Box 64, Folder 13)
  - Knights and Daughters of Tabor — Bulletins, Programs (Box 64, Folder 14 - 15)
  - Knights and Daughters of Tabor - - Correspondence (Box 64, Folder 16)
  - Knights and Daughters of Tabor — Minutes: Monthly Messages and Rulings by P.M Smith, 1938 - 19939 (Box 64, Folder 17)
  - Knights and Daughters of Tabor — Minutes: Monthly Messages and Rulings by P.M Smith, 1940 - 1942 (Box 64, Folder 18)
  - Knights and Daughters of Tabor - - Minutes: Monthly Messages and Rulings by P.M Smith, 1943 - 1944 (Box 64, Folder 19)
  - Knights and Daughters of Tabor - - Minutes: Monthly Messages and Rulings by P.M Smith, 1945 - 1946 (Box 64, Folder 20)
  - Knights and Daughters of Tabor - - Minutes: Monthly Messages and Rulings by P.M Smith, 1947 (Box 64, Folder 21)
  - Knights and Daughters of Tabor - - Minutes: Monthly Messages and Rulings by P.M Smith, 1948 (Box 64, Folder 22)
  - Knights and Daughters of Tabor - - Minutes: Monthly Messages and Rulings by P.M Smith, 1949 (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - Knights and Daughters of Tabor - - Minutes: Monthly Messages and Rulings by P.M Smith, 1950 (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - Knights and Daughters of Tabor - - Minutes; Fragments, undated (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - Knights and Daughters of Tabor — P.M. (Perry Monroe) Smith, Chief Grand Mentor (and Father of KMS) (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Knights and Daughters of Tabor - - Quarterly Reports (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - Knights and Daughters of Tabor - - Tabvorian Hospital, Mound Bayou, MS (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - Labor Department - - Nashville Regional Staff Committee (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - Laborers international - - Nashville Regional Staff Committee (Box 65, Folder 8)
  - Law and Justice - - Ad Hoc Committee (Box 65, Folder 9)
  - Leadership Nashville, 1977 (Box 65, Folder 10 - 11)
  - Leadership Nashville, 1977 - 1978 (Box 65, Folder 12)
  - Leadership Nashville, 1978 (Box 65, Folder 13)
  - Leadership Nashville, 1979 (Box 65, Folder 14)
  - Leadership Nashville, 1980 (Box 65, Folder 15)
  - Leadership Nashville, 1981 (Box 65, Folder 16)
  - LeMoyne-Owen College - - Development Program (Box 65, Folder 17)
  - Library of Congress (Box 65, Folder 18)
  - Love, Lafayette (Box 65, Folder 19)
  - Manna (Box 65, Folder 20)
  - Manpower Advisory Council (Box 65, Folder 21)
  - March of Dimes (Box 65, Folder 22)
  - Martin Luther King, Jr. Afro-American Preaching Series (Boston University) (Box 65, Folder 23)
  - Martin Luther King, Jr. Afro-American Preaching Series (Boston University) (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Martin Luther King, Jr. Center for Social Change (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - Martin Luther King, Jr. Center for Social Change, 1976 - 1978 (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - Martin Luther King, Jr. Center for Social Change, 1979 (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Martin Luther King, Jr. Center for Social Change, 1981 (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - Martin Luther King, Jr. Center for Social Change, 1982 (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - Martin Luther King, Jr. Center for Social Change, 1983 (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - Martin Luther King, Jr. Center for Social Change, 1983 - 1984 Campaign (Box 66, Folder 8)
  - Martin Luther King, Jr. Memorial Center, 1969 - 1970 (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - Martin Luther King, Jr. Memorial Dinner and Consultation, 1975 (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - Martin Luther King, Jr., Observance, 1976 (Box 66, Folder 11)
  - Martin Luther King, Jr., Observance, 1979 (Box 66, Folder 12)
  - Material on Dr. Harold D. West (Box 66, Folder 13)
  - Matthew Walker Health Center (Box 66, Folder 14)
  - McKinney, Samuel (Dr.) (Box 66, Folder 15)
  - McKissack Reading and Math Program (Box 66, Folder 16)
  - Medical Committee for Human Rights (Box 66, Folder 17)
  - Meharry Community Mental Health Center (Box 66, Folder 18)
  - Meharry Department of Anatomy - - Bequeathal (Box 66, Folder 19)
  - Meharry Medical College, 1975 - 1976 (Box 66, Folder 20)
  - Meharry Medical College, 1977 (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - Meharry Medical College, 1978 - 1981 (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - Meharry Medical College - - Clippings (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - Meharry Medical College - - Maternal and Child Health/Family Planning (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - Meharry Medical College Fund (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - Meharry-Mound Bayou (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - Memorabilia (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - Mennonite Central Committee (Box 67, Folder 8)
  - Metropolitan Action Commission, 1965 (Box 67, Folder 9)
  - - 12 Metropolitan Action Committee, 1966 (Box 67, Folder 10)
  - Metropolitan Action Commission - - Lilmon Ester (Box 67, Folder 13)
  - Metropolitan Council (Box 67, Folder 14)
  - Metropolitan Government of Nashville and Davidson County (Box 67, Folder 15)
  - Metropolitan Human Relations Commission, 1979 (Box 67, Folder 16)
  - Metropolitan Human Relations Commission, 1980 (Box 67, Folder 17)
  - Metropolitan Human Relations Commission, 1981 (Box 67, Folder 18)
  - Metropolitan Human Relations Committee (Box 67, Folder 19)
  - Metropolitan Ministers Conference (Box 67, Folder 20)
  - Metropolitan Nashville Community Education Task Force (Box 67, Folder 21)
  - Metropolitan Nashville Councilmen, 1968 (Box 67, Folder 22)
  - Metropolitan Police Department (Box 67, Folder 23)
  - Metropolitan Schools, 1956 - 1979 (Box 68, Folder 1 - 9)
  - Metropolitan Schools, 1980 (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - Metropolitan Schools and Citizens Advisory Committee (Box 69, Folder 2 - 6)
  - Metropolitan Schools, 1979 (Box 69, Folder 7 - 13)
  - Metropolitan Transit Committee, 1972 (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - Metropolitan Transit Committee, 1973 (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Middle Tennessee Business Association (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Middle Tennessee Business Association (Operation Northtown) (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - Middle Tennessee Diabetes Association (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - Middle Tennessee Long Term Care/Gerontology Center — "Aging News" (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - Mid-South Automobile Club, Inc. (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - Ministers — Names and Addresses (Box 70, Folder 8)
  - Ministers Life (Box 70, Folder 9)
  - Minister's Parade, 1962 (Box 70, Folder 10)
  - Ministers to Blacks in Higher Education, 1972 - 1976 (Box 70, Folder 11)
  - Ministers to Blacks in Higher Education, 1976 - 1980 (Box 70, Folder 12)
  - Minority Business Enterprise (Box 70, Folder 13)
  - Minority Economic Development Corp. (MEDCO), 1971 (Box 70, Folder 14 - 15)
  - Minority Economic Development Corp. (MEDCO), 1972 (Box 70, Folder 16 - 17)
  - Minority Economic Development Corp. (MEDCO), 1973 (Box 70, Folder 18)
  - Minority Economic Development Corp. (MEDCO), 1973 (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Minority Economic Development Corp. (MEDCO), 1974 (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Minority Economic Development Corp. (MEDCO) — Report and Proposal, 1974 (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - Minority Economic Development Corp. (MEDCO), 1975 (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - Minority Economic Development Corp. (MEDCO), 1976 (Box 71, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 71, Folder 6 - 11)
  - Mississippi Baptist Seminary (Box 71, Folder 12)
  - Mississippi State University (Box 71, Folder 13)
  - Model Cities (Box 71, Folder 14)
  - Model Cities Responder, 1971 - 1975 (Box 71, Folder 15)
  - Montgomery Improvement Association (Box 71, Folder 16)
  - Monthly Report on the Baptist Student Union in the Higher Institutions of Learning In and Near Nashville, TN (Box 71, Folder 17)
  - Morehouse College, 1960s (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Morehouse College, 1970s (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - Morehouse College Bulletins, 1957 - 1964 (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - Morehouse College — Clippings (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - Morehouse School of Religion — Board of Directors (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - Morehouse School of Religion — Board of Directors (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - Morehouse School of Religion, 1975 (Box 72, Folder 7)
  - Morehouse School of Religion, 1976 (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - Morehouse School of Religion, 1977 - 1979 (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - Morehouse School of Religion, 1980 - 1981 (Box 72, Folder 10)
  - Morehouse School of Religion, 1982 - 1984 (Box 72, Folder 11)
  - Morehouse School of Religion — Clippings (Box 72, Folder 12)
  - Morton, William (Polytech) (Box 72, Folder 13)
  - Mound Bayou — Clippings (Box 72, Folder 14)
  - Mound Bayou Community Hospital (Box 72, Folder 15)
  - Mount Zion Baptist Church, Seattle, WA — Publications (Box 72, Folder 16)
  - Nashville American Revolution Bicentennial Commission, 1974 (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - Nashville American Revolution Bicentennial Commission, 1975 (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - Nashville American Revolution Bicentennial Commission, 1976 (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - Nashville Association of Churches (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - Nashville Association of Rabbis, Priests and Ministers (NARPM), 1975 (Box 73, Folder 5 - 6)
  - Nashville Association of Rabbis, Priests and Ministers (NARPM), 1976 (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - Nashville Association of Rabbis, Priests and Ministers (NARPM), 1977 - 1979 (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - Nashville Community Relations Council (Box 73, Folder 9 - 10)
  - Nashville Council of Colored Parent-Teacher Associations (Box 73, Folder 11)
  - Nashville Foreign Policy Conference (Box 73, Folder 12)
  - Nashville Heritage Project (Box 73, Folder 13)
  - Nashville League of Women Voters (Box 73, Folder 14)
  - Nashville Opportunities Industrialization Center, Inc. (OIC) — Annual Report, 1977 - 1978 (Box 73, Folder 15)
  - Nashville Opportunities Industrialization Center, Inc. (OIC) — Annual Report, 1979; Fundraising Statistics (Box 73, Folder 16)
  - Nashville Opportunities Industrialization Center, Inc. (OIC) — Clippings (Box 73, Folder 17)
  - Nashville Religious Economic Statistics (Box 73, Folder 18)
  - Nashville Symphony (Box 73, Folder 19)
  - Nashville Urban League, Inc., 1968 (Box 73, Folder 20)
  - Nashville Urban League, Inc., 1969 (Box 73, Folder 21 - 22)
  - Nashville Urban League, Inc., 1970 (Box 73, Folder 23)
  - Nashville Christian Leadership Council
  - Nashville Christian Leadership Conference, Affiliate Leaders Conference (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - Annual New Year's Breakfast, Clarks Memorial Methodist Church, 1963 (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - Application for Funds Form (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - Bank Statements, 1960 (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - Bank Statements, 1961 (Box 74, Folder 5)
  - Bank Statements, 1960 - 1961 (Box 74, Folder 6)
  - Bank Statements, 1962 (Box 74, Folder 7)
  - Bank Statements, 1963 (Box 74, Folder 8)
  - Bank Statements, 1964 (Box 74, Folder 9)
  - Belafonte Concert, Financial Report (Box 74, Folder 10)
  - Board Members, 1963 - 1964 (Box 74, Folder 11)
  - Board Minutes, 1960 - 1961 (Box 74, Folder 12)
  - Board Minutes, 1962 (Box 74, Folder 13)
  - Board Minutes, 1963 (Box 74, Folder 14)
  - Board Minutes, 1964 (Box 74, Folder 15)
  - Bombingham, AL (Box 74, Folder 16)
  - Bowling Material (Box 74, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence: Andrew White, Incoming - Adams, Inez - King, Martin Luther, Jr. (Box 74, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence: Andrew White, Incoming - Lennox, Anne E.-Wright, S.J. (Box 74, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence: Andrew White, Outgoing - February-December 1963 (Box 74, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence: Andrew White, Outgoing - January-February 1964 (Box 74, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence: Andrew White, Outgoing - March-May 1964 (Box 74, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence: Andrew White, Outgoing - June-July 1964, undated (Box 74, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence: Contribution Letters (Baker, Rachel - Walker, Matthew) (Box 74, Folder 24)
  - Nashville Christian Leadership Conference, Correspondence: Letters of Acknowledgement (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence: Letters of Acknowledgment (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence: Miscellaneous, Incoming (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence: Miscellaneous, Outgoing (Box 75, Folder 4 - 5)
  - Employer-Employee Relations Committee, Nashville Area Chamber of Commerce (Box 75, Folder 6)
  - Equality Buttons — Sales Records (Box 75, Folder 7)
  - Fifth Anniversary Program (November 17, 1963) (Box 75, Folder 8)
  - Financial Statements 1962 - 1964; Adding Machine Records (Box 75, Folder 9)
  - Flyers (Box 75, Folder 10)
  - Freedom Riders (Box 75, Folder 11)
  - Fundraising (Box 75, Folder 12)
  - General Information (Box 75, Folder 13)
  - Information on "The Technique of Non-Violence as Applied in Nashville" (Box 75, Folder 14)
  - Integrated Places (Box 75, Folder 15)
  - Interview at J.W. Carters; Interview — Restaurant Association (Box 75, Folder 16)
  - Mass Meeting Donations (Reports) (Box 75, Folder 17)
  - Mass Meeting Programs (1960 - 1963) (Box 75, Folder 18)
  - Mass Meeting Programs (1963) (Box 75, Folder 19)
  - Mass Meeting Programs (1964, undated) (Box 75, Folder 20)
  - Ministers Committee (Box 75, Folder 21)
  - Minutes, 1958 - 1959 (Box 75, Folder 22)
  - Minutes, 1960 (Box 75, Folder 23)
  - Minutes, 1961 (Box 75, Folder 24)
  - Minutes, 1962 (Box 75, Folder 25)
  - Minutes, 1963 (Box 75, Folder 26)
  - Nashville Christian Leadership Conference, Minutes, Duplicates, 1959 - 1960 (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - Minutes, Duplicates, 1960 (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Minutes, Duplicates, 1961 (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - Minutes, Duplicates, 1961 - 1962 (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous Drafts (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous Items (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous Notes (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - Newsletter: The Voices of the Movement, 1961 (Box 76, Folder 8)
  - Newsletter: The Voices of the Movement, 1962 (Box 76, Folder 9)
  - Newsletter: The Voices of the Movement, 1963, miscellaneous related notes (Box 76, Folder 10)
  - Official Directory, Board Members, 1963 (Box 76, Folder 11)
  - Petitions Sent to Washington, D.C., 1963: undated petition (Box 76, Folder 12)
  - Petty Cash (Box 76, Folder 13)
  - Pilgrimage (Box 76, Folder 14)
  - Pledges Paid Out, 1962 (Box 76, Folder 15)
  - Pledge Record, 1962 (Box 76, Folder 16)
  - Pledges Record, 1962, undated (Box 76, Folder 17)
  - Postage Meter Record Book (Box 76, Folder 18)
  - Press Release (Box 76, Folder 19)
  - Program Committee (Box 76, Folder 20)
  - Projects Committee (Box 76, Folder 21)
  - Proposals to the Nashville Community (Box 76, Folder 22)
  - Receipts, 1959 - 1963 (Box 76, Folder 23)
  - Records: "The Nashville Sit-In Story" (Box 76, Folder 24)
  - Nashville Christian Leadership Conference, Remarks/Addresses by Andrew White (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - Report on Current Events (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - Resolutions (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - Segregated Places (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - Songs (Box 77, Folder 5)
  - Statement of Purpose: Nashville Non-Violent Movement; Student Movement Newsletter (SNCC); miscellaneous other newsletters (Box 77, Folder 6)
  - Stationary (Box 77, Folder 7)
  - Students (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Telephone Committee (Box 77, Folder 9)
  - Transportation List (Box 77, Folder 10)
  - Volunteered Workers (Box 77, Folder 11)
  - National Anthem of Nigeria (Box 77, Folder 12)
  - National Anti-Klan Network (Box 77, Folder 13)
  - National Association for the Advancement for Colored People (NAACP) (Box 77, Folder 14 - 17)
  - National Association for the Advancement for Colored People (NAACP) - - Pamphlets, Flyers, Brochures (Box 77, Folder 18)
  - National Association for the Advancement for Colored People (NAACP) Legal Defense and Education Fund (Press Releases), 1961 - 1964 (Box 77, Folder 19 - 21)
  - National Baptist Churches (Box 77, Folder 22)
  - National Baptist Convention, USA, 1948 - 1962 (Box 77, Folder 23 - 24)
  - National Baptist Convention (94th Annual Session), 1974 (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - National Baptist Convention (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - National Baptist Convention — Publications (Baptist Progress) (Box 78, Folder 3)
  - National Baptist Convention — Publications (National Baptist Voice) (Box 78, Folder 4)
  - National Basic Skills Conference — Nashville (Box 78, Folder 5)
  - National Black Christian Student Leadership Consultation (Box 78, Folder 6)
  - National Black United Fund (Box 78, Folder 7)
  - National Committee of Black Churchmen (later National Conference of Black Churchmen), 1969 - 1979 (Box 78, Folder 8 - 14)
  - Leadership Enhancement Program, 1979 (Box 78, Folder 15)
  - National Committee of Black Churchmen (later National Conference of Black Churchmen), 1980 (Box 78, Folder 16 - 18)
  - Membership, 1981 (Box 78, Folder 19)
  - National Committee of Black Churchmen (later National Conference of Black Churchmen), 1982 (Box 78, Folder 20 - 21)
  - Undated materials; Stationary; Notes for brochure; Unclassified notes (Box 78, Folder 22)
  - National Conference of Christians and Jews (Box 79, Folder 1 - 2)
  - National Conference on Religion and Race (Box 79, Folder 3)
  - National Council of Churches (NCC) (Box 79, Folder 4 - 6)
  - President's Panel (Box 79, Folder 7 - 9)
  - Unit Committee — Director of Church Society (Box 79, Folder 10)
  - Kenyon C. Burke (Box 79, Folder 11 - 12)
  - National Cultural Liberation Movement (Box 79, Folder 13)
  - National Institute for Campus Ministries (Box 79, Folder 14)
  - National Inter - Denominational Ministerial Alliance (Box 79, Folder 15)
  - National Preaching Convocation - 1982 — American Baptist Convention (Box 79, Folder 16)
  - National Urban League (Box 79, Folder 17)
  - The New White Person (Study Paper for NETWORK Friends) (Box 79, Folder 18)
  - News Releases (Box 79, Folder 19)
  - News Releases, 1979 (Box 79, Folder 20)
  - 1983 March on Washington (Box 79, Folder 21)
  - North Nashville Athletic Association (Box 80, Folder 1)
  - Northern Negro Leadership Conference (Detroit Council for Human Rights) (Box 80, Folder 2)
  - Oasis House (Box 80, Folder 3)
  - Oberlin College Material (Box 80, Folder 4)
  - OPEN Society (Box 80, Folder 5)
  - Operation Breadbasket (Box 80, Folder 6)
  - Operation Comeback (Box 80, Folder 7)
  - Operation Open City, 1960 - 1963, undated (Box 80, Folder 8 - 12)
  - Job Opportunities for Negroes (Box 80, Folder 13)
  - Operation PUSH - Nashville (Box 80, Folder 14)
  - Operation PUSH (Box 80, Folder 15)
  - Opportunities Industrialization Centers of America (Box 80, Folder 16)
  - Outlook Nashville, Inc. (Box 80, Folder 17)
  - Outside Mission Groups (Box 80, Folder 18)
  - Overseas Personnel Recruitment Office (Box 80, Folder 19)
  - Owen College, 1964 - 1967 (Box 80, Folder 20 - 23)
  - Palaver Club (Box 80, Folder 24)
  - Papers from "Preaching from Unexpected Places" (Box 80, Folder 25)
  - Papers on Social Issues (Box 80, Folder 26 - 27)
  - Papers on Social Issues (Box 81, Folder 1 - 2)
  - Partners in Housing (Box 81, Folder 3)
  - Pastor's Continuing Education (Box 81, Folder 4)
  - Pastoral Counseling Program (Box 81, Folder 5)
  - Pastors School (Box 81, Folder 6)
  - Peace Corps Perspective (Box 81, Folder 7)
  - Petition for Justice (Box 81, Folder 8)
  - Petition for Reinstatement of Students at Tennessee AandI (Box 81, Folder 9)
  - Petitions - - Public Accommodations (Box 81, Folder 10)
  - P.M. Smith Memorial Scholarship Fund, 1971 - 1976 (Box 81, Folder 11 - 22)
  - Correspondence, 1976 (Box 81, Folder 23 - 24)
  - Expenses, 1976 (Box 81, Folder 25)
  - Receipts, 1976 (Box 81, Folder 26)
  - Chicago Committee, 1976 (Box 81, Folder 27)
  - P.M. Smith Memorial Scholarship Fund -- Detroit Committee, 1976 (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - Gary Committee, 1976 (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - Memphis Committee, 1976 (Box 82, Folder 3)
  - Nashville Committee, 1976 (Box 82, Folder 4)
  - Nashville Committee, 1977 (Box 82, Folder 5)
  - Contributions, 1977 (Box 82, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1977 (Box 82, Folder 7)
  - Receipts, 1977 (Box 82, Folder 8)
  - Expenses, 1977 (Box 82, Folder 9)
  - Nashville Committee, 1977 (Box 82, Folder 10)
  - Nashville Committee, 1978 (Box 82, Folder 11)